# ANDI SISWANTO

#### **ADDRESS**

Gg. H. Naban Komplek Pondok Lakah Permai, Ciledug - Tangerang

### **EMAIL**

andisis92@gmail.com

## **PHONE**

+6285290919260

## LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andisis wanto

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://andisis.github.io

## **ABOUT**

I am a programmer with 6 years experience, I have passion in programming, fast learning, honest, loyal and responsible

## **SKILLS**

HTML – CSS – JavaScript – Bootstrap – jQuery – PHP – MySQL – Codelgniter – Phonegap – React Native – Linux – SEO – Photoshop

# **EXPERIENCE**

# PRODUCTION MANAGER - PT. HADI MUDA BERKARYA

December 2015 - October 2018

- Control the work of the production team
- Set the timeline of the production team
- Assisting production team work when the project is overloaded
- Build internal website

# WEB DEVELOPER - PT. BERLIAN KURNIA BAKTI

March 2014 - September 2015

- Running SEO for client websites
- Build Ecommerce CMS for clients and internal
- Build website for clients

# WEB PROGRAMMER - PT. ADVANTEL NUSANTARA

December 2012 - February 2014

- Create documentation for existing projects
- Installing a server using CentOS
- Build financial report application for internal
- Test the Android & iOS application created by the team (UAT)

# JUNIOR PROGRAMMER - PT. MYNTS SOLUSINDO

May 2012 - November 2012

- Slicing PSD to HTML
- Build internal website (ecommerce)
- Running SEO for internal websites

# **EDUCATION**

## 2007 - 2010

SMK Pelayaran Samudera Cilacap